Andreas Marsh

Computer Science Honors Undergraduate Student

SUMMARY

I am a third-year honors student at the University of Georgia studying Computer Science and have training and experience in both Java, C++, and Swift programming.

I love creating applications that others can interact with and explore and have recently begun the development of a personal website/blog as a side project. I have also consistently received high marks on projects for both Android and iOS app development courses that I am taking this Spring. Feel free to check out my GitHub to see some of the projects that I've been working on.

Through years of working at summer camps, I have developed great leadership, communication, and teamwork skills, being able to create environments where everybody feels both included and valued.

EXPERIENCE



Glisson Camp & Retreat Center, Dahlonega, GA — *Camp Counselor*

May 2019 - July 2019

- worked with children and adults with mild to moderate developmental disabilities
- created an environment that uplifted campers and allowed their uniqueness to shine



Glisson Camp & Retreat Center, Dahlonega, GA — *Camp Crew*

May 2018 - July 2018

- performed various jobs and tasks around camp to have it run smoothly
- lifeguarded, helped facilitate high ropes course, set up and cleaned the dining hall, and other jobs
- had a major impact on preparing me for college and how to balance a schedule, work within a group, and gain an overall greater understanding of managing the new independence and responsibilities you're given in college

EDUCATION / CERTIFICATION



The University of Georgia, Athens, GA — BS Computer Science

August 2018 - May 2022



New Media Institute, Athens, GA — New Media Certificate (Dev Track)

August 2018 - May 2022

CONTACT

124 North Poplar St Athens, GA, 30601 (404) 502-0710 marsh.andreas.s@gmail.com

GITHUB / WEBSITE

github.com/andreasmarsh

andreasmarsh.com

SKILLS

Java

C++

Swift

Android Studio

XCode

Adobe XD

HONORS & AWARDS

Honors Program
Member of UGA's Honor
Program
August 2018 - Present

Dean's ListSpring Semester 2020

Charter Scholarship Recipient
Awarded for outstanding
achievement in academics to
2% of new students

LANGUAGES

English (high proficiency)
German (moderate proficiency)